<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<completion prefix="gara.jswt.JSWT" extends="">
<item repl="ABORT" display="ABORT"><![CDATA[The MessageBox style constant for an ABORT button; the only valid combination is ABORT|RETRY|IGNORE (value is 1<<9).]]></item>
<item repl="APPLICATION_MODAL" display="APPLICATION_MODAL"><![CDATA[Style constant for application modal behavior (value is 1<<16).]]></item>
<item repl="BOTTOM" display="BOTTOM"><![CDATA[Style constant for align bottom behavior (value is 1<<10, since align DOWN and align BOTTOM are considered the same).]]></item>
<item repl="CANCEL" display="CANCEL"><![CDATA[The MessageBox style constant for a CANCEL button, valid combinations are OK|CANCEL, YES|NO|CANCEL, RETRY|CANCEL (value is 1<<8).]]></item>
<item repl="CLOSE" display="CLOSE"><![CDATA[Style constant for close box trim (value is 1<<6, since we do not distinguish between CLOSE style and MENU style).]]></item>
<item repl="DEFAULT" display="DEFAULT"><![CDATA[Indicates that a default should be used (value is 0).

NOTE: In SWT, this value is -1, but that causes problems with bitwise JavaScript operators...]]></item>
<item repl="DOWN" display="DOWN"><![CDATA[Style constant for align down behavior (value is 1<<10, since align DOWN and align BOTTOM are considered the same).]]></item>
<item repl="DRAG" display="DRAG"><![CDATA[Indicates that a user-interface component is being dragged, for example dragging the thumb of a scroll bar (value is 1).]]></item>
<item repl="FULL_SELECTION" display="FULL_SELECTION"><![CDATA[Style constant for full row selection behavior (value is 1<<16).]]></item>
<item repl="IGNORE" display="IGNORE"><![CDATA[The MessageBox style constant for an IGNORE button, the only valid combination is ABORT|RETRY|IGNORE (value is 1<<11).]]></item>
<item repl="MENU" display="MENU"><![CDATA[Style constant for shell menu trim (value is 1<<6, since we do not distinguish between CLOSE style and MENU style).]]></item>
<item repl="MULTI" display="MULTI"><![CDATA[Style constant for multi-selection behavior in lists and multiple line support on text fields (value is 1<<1).]]></item>
<item repl="NO" display="NO"><![CDATA[The MessageBox style constant for NO button, valid combinations are YES|NO, YES|NO|CANCEL (value is 1<<7).]]></item>
<item repl="OK" display="OK"><![CDATA[The MessageBox style constant for an OK button, valid combinations are OK, OK|CANCEL (value is 1<<5).]]></item>
<item repl="RETRY" display="RETRY"><![CDATA[The MessageBox style constant for a RETRY button, valid combinations are ABORT|RETRY|IGNORE, RETRY|CANCEL (value is 1<<10).]]></item>
<item repl="SINGLE" display="SINGLE"><![CDATA[Style constant for single selection behavior in lists and single line support on text fields (value is 1<<2).]]></item>
<item repl="SYSTEM_MODAL" display="SYSTEM_MODAL"><![CDATA[Style constant for system modal behavior (value is 1<<17).]]></item>
<item repl="TOP" display="TOP"><![CDATA[Style constant for align top behavior (value is 1<<7, since align UP and align TOP are considered the same).]]></item>
<item repl="UP" display="UP"><![CDATA[Style constant for align up behavior (value is 1<<7, since align UP and align TOP are considered the same).]]></item>
<item repl="YES" display="YES"><![CDATA[The MessageBox style constant for YES button, valid combinations are YES|NO, YES|NO|CANCEL (value is 1<<6).]]></item>
</completion>
